const data = [
        {
                question: "How long do ‘The Custom Websites’ take to build a website?",
                answer: "A. The time taken to complete a web design and development is decided by many factors. Availability of content, your efforts, and constant feedback, all these factors decide the completion time. Besides, the more complex the site is, the more time will be required."
        },
        {
                question: "How much does a website cost?",
                answer: "A. The cost of a website depends on many factors. No true developer can give you a quote directly without discussing the factors. To get a better idea about the cost of a website, you can:<ul><li>Email us your requirements or call us on the given contact number.</li><li>                Tell us your needs regarding the website i.e, the nature of your website, web design, and features.</li><li>We will provide an initial ballpark figure.</li><li>If you agree, we will provide the final quote based on your needs</li></ul>."
        },
        {
                question: "Will THE CUSTOM WEBSITES provide a free SEO audit of a website?",
                answer: "A. Yes! We can perform an SEO audit to understand where your website stands and what strategies can we adopt to make it better."
        },
        {
                question: "How can I get updates about my web project?",
                answer: "A. Based on the requirements of your web project, we will assign the work to an expert who will stay in touch with you during the development process and keep you updated about the progress."
        },
        {
                question: "Do I own my website?",
                answer: "A. Of course! The website built is 100% owned by you. If you want any other company to service your site, we will happily help you in making the transition. After all, you are the owner of your website and you can take it wherever you want."
        },
        {
                question: "Do you offer domain registration and website hosting services?",
                answer: "A. No! We do not offer domain registration or web hosting services to our clients."
        },
        {
                question: "Will my website be mobile-friendly?",
                answer: "A. Absolutely! We understand the importance of having a mobile-friendly website in today’s world. Our experts work hard to ensure that your website looks great on all devices including smartphones, tablets, and desktops."
        },
        {
                question: "Does The Custom Websites provide long-term support after completing the project?",
                answer: "A. Yes! We do. We aren’t going anywhere after the launch of your website. The Custom Websites is a professional web development company - doing this for many years now. We are only a mail away. You can seek our help whenever you need it."
        },
        {
                question: "How do websites make money?",
                answer: "A. There are three basic ways of making money from websites:<ol><li>Affiliate Marketing - receive payment from merchants as a result of the sale of the product you linked on your website.</li> <li>Advertising</li> <li>E-commerce - Generate revenue through selling products and services directly.</li> </ol>"
        },
        {
                question: "What’s the procedure for creating a new website?",
                answer: "A. The process of creating a new website works in the following steps:<ul><li>Choose your niche and domain name.</li><li>Register your website under your domain name.</li><li>Choose a hosting service.</li><li>Choose a platform (like WordPress) and install it.</li><li>Choose themes and features.</li><li>Add information/content.</li>"
        },
        {
                question: "What technologies do ‘The Custom Websites’ use for web development?",
                answer: "A. ‘The Custom Websites’ experts provide web development services using the latest technologies to keep pace with the growing digitized world. We build websites using WordPress, Drupal, Java, PHP, Node.js, HTML 5, React.Js, .Net, etc."
        },
        {
                question: "Do you offer SEO services?",
                answer: "A. Yes! Being the top Digital Marketing Agency, we offer professional small business SEO services to help businesses get more traffic, more leads, and grow quickly. We target both on-page as well as off-page SEO and provide services like keyword research, content marketing, social media marketing, technical SEO, and more."
        },
        {
                question: "What type of businesses can you help?",
                answer: "A. No matter from which niche you belong, we have experts to cover every niche and help owners establish an ever-growing business. Business industries we help include Education, Health Care, Real Estate, Corporation sector, Fitness, Travel, and Restaurants."
        },
        {
                question: "Do you work with platforms like WordPress, Joomla, Drupal, WIX?",
                answer: "A. Yes! We have experts of each platform armed with outstanding skills. ‘The Custom Websites’ is dedicated to helping business owners establish ever-growing businesses that generate great revenues."
        },
        {
                question: "Can you help revamp/update my existing website?",
                answer: "A. We provide effective web solutions for your existing website and revamp it into one according to your requirements and needs. If you don’t like your existing web design, we can discuss everything and once you approve the design that we provide, we can start redesigning your website."
        },
        {
                question: "Do I have to be local to work with you?",
                answer: "A. No, you don’t need to be necessarily local to work with us. Our whole team works remotely and we provide outstanding services to clients all over the world."
        },
        {
                question: "When do I pay?",
                answer: "A. We will decide with milestones."
        },
        {
                question: "Is ‘The Custom Websites’ providing dedicated developers?",
                answer: "A. Yes! Our experts are dedicated to performing every task as per the requirements of our client. If you have a roadmap for your business, contact us and tell us your story. Hire our expert developers - they will listen to you carefully - design a website or application that will help grow your online business and reach a wider audience to boost your sales."
        },
        {
                question: "How much important is a website for business?",
                answer: "A. Having a well-built website will enable your customers to know more about your products and services. Businesses with a website are considered more credible as it builds trust among your customers."
        },
];

export default data;
